Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Additional Photographs 5917 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Joint Board Xmas Party - Dec. 1971 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  was b20ff7 -- 3 photographs
- Joint Board Xmas Party - 12/1978 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  was b20ff8 -- 5 photographs
- Jt. Bd. Conference - Jan. 1950 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  was b20ff9 -- 3 photographs
- Jt. Bd. Conf., 1951 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  was b20ff10 -- 1 photograph
- Jt. Bd. Conf. - Feb. 10, 1952 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  was b20ff11 -- 12 photographs
- 1953 Annual Conf. (Box 30, Folder 28)
  was b20ff12 -- 13 photographs
- Jt. Bd. Conf., 1984 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  was b20ff13 -- 6 photographs
- 11th Annual Jt. Bd. Conference - Feb. 6, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  was b20ff14 -- 13 photographs
- Jt. Bd. Annual Conf. Pictures - April 13, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  was b20ff15 -- 4 photographs
- Jt. Bd. Annual conf. Pix -- April 13, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  was b20ff16 -- 7 photographs
- Joint Board Conference, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  was b20ff17 -- 25 photographs
- Joint Board Conference, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  was b20ff18 -- 13 photographs
- Joint Board Conference, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  was b20ff19 -- 10 photographs
- Joint Board Conference, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  was b20ff20 - 5 photographs
- Joint Board conference - Oct. 1963 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  was b20ff21 -- 25 photographs
- Joint Board Conference -- 1/21/1967 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  was b20ff22 -- 17 photographs
- Joint Board Annual Conference -- 2/10/1968 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  was b20ff23 -- 13 photographs
- Joint Board Dance - Royal Windsor (Box 31, Folder 5)
  was b20ff24 -- 4 photographs
- Joint Board Delegates - IFLWU Conventions (Box 31, Folder 6)
  was b20ff25 -- 3 photographs
- Joint Board Division Board Meeting - Oct. 1969 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  was b20ff26 -- 1 photographs
- Joint Board Elections (Box 31, Folder 8)
  was b20ff27 -- 2 photographs
- Joint Board Installation Meeting - June 12, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  was b20ff28 -- 4 photographs
- Joint Board Installation Meeting - June 8, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  was b20ff29 -- 13 photographs
- Jt. Bd. Installation and max Salzman Tribute -- 9/22/1978 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  was b20ff30
- Joint Board Italian - American Committee (Box 31, Folder 12)
  was b20ff31 -- 2 photographs
- Local Meetings (1) (Box 31, Folder 13)
  was b20ff32 -- 26 photographs
- Local Meetings (2) (Box 31, Folder 14)
  was b20ff32 -- 24 photographs
- Local Meetings (3) (Box 31, Folder 15)
  was b20ff32 -- 22 photographs
- Local Meetings (4) (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Joint Board Leaders (Box 31, Folder 17)
  was b20ff33 -- 6 photographs
- Joint Board Annual Meeting -- 2/22/1969 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  was b20ff34 -- 28 photographs
- Joint Board Meeting -- Oct. 6, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  was b20ff35 -- 4 photographs
- Joint Board Meeting - Elections - Oct. 1970 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  was b20ff36 -- 9 photographs
- Jt. Div. Bd. Meeting - 3 N.Y. Division -- 11/14/1978 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  was b20ff37
- Joint Board News Pix Summer 1963 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  was b20ff38 -- 5 photographs
- Joint Board News Pix Spring 1963 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  was b20ff39 -- 5 photographs
- Joint Board News -- Fall 1964 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  was b20ff40 -- 6 photographs
- Joint Board News Dec. 1966 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  was b20ff41 -- 5 photographs
- Joint Board Office Opening -- 1/31/1953 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  was b20ff42 -- 7 photographs
- Joint Board Pictures (Box 31, Folder 27)
  was b20ff43 -- 11 photographs
- Joint Board Staff (Box 31, Folder 28)
  was b20ff44 - EMPTY
- Joint Board 25th Anniv. (Box 31, Folder 29)
  was b20ff45 -- 3 photographs
- Joint Board Women's Committee (Box 31, Folder 30)
  was b20ff46-- 1 photograph
- Joint Council (Box 31, Folder 31)
  was b20ff47 -- 11 photographs
- Joint Council Children's Programs (Box 31, Folder 32)
  was b20ff48 -- 3 photographs
- Joint Council Cultural Activities (Box 31, Folder 33)
  was b20ff49 -- 16 photographs
- Joint Council Meetings, Oct. 8-9 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  was b20ff50 -- 4 photographs
- Joint Council - Misc. (Box 31, Folder 35)
  was b20ff51 -- EMPTY
- Joint Council Retirees Meeting - 3/16/1988 (Box 31, Folder 36)
  was b20ff52 -- 5 photographs
- Joint Council Social Events (Box 31, Folder 37)
  was b20ff53 -- 16 photographs
- Joint Defense Appeal in honor of Henry Foner, Sidney Dickler (Box 31, Folder 38)
  was b20ff54 -- 3 photographs
- Joint Executive Board Meeting - 1 FLM, 5 FJC - 11/1985 (Box 31, Folder 39)
  was b20ff55 -- 7 photographs
- Joint Membership Meeting - All Locals -- 10/14/1965 (Box 31, Folder 40)
  was b20ff56 -- 12 photographs
- Joint Membership Meeting - Penn Gardens Hotel - (3 N.Y. Divisions) - December 14, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 41)
  was b20ff57 -- 4 photographs
- Joint Meeting Div. Boards - Nov. 14, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 42)
  was b20ff58 -- 2 photographs
- Joint Meeting Locals - 1-2-3 (Box 31, Folder 43)
  was b20ff59 -- 3 photographs
- Kennedy Memorial meeting - 11/25/1963 (1) (Box 32, Folder 1)
  was b20ff60 -- 26 photographs
- Kennedy Memorial Meeting -- 11/25/1963 (2) (Box 32, Folder 2)
  was b20ff61 -- 13 photographs
- King Memorial - April 1968 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  was b20ff62 -- 23 photographs
- King Memorial Meeting - Jan. 15, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  was b20ff62 -- 7 photographs
- King Movie - March 1970 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  was b20ff63 -- 5 photographs
- Sarah King Commencement - 6/23/1983 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  was b20ff64 -- 4 photographs
- Myer Klig New Eng. Dist. 1, IFLWU (Box 32, Folder 7)
  was b20ff65 - 2 photographs
- Louise Kramer Exhibit (Box 32, Folder 8)
  was b20ff66 -- 1 photograph
- Labor Day - 1986 - Central Park (Box 32, Folder 9)
  was b20ff67 -- 3 photographs
- Labor Day March, N.C. 1976 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  was b20ff68 -- 6 photographs; news clippings
- Labor Day Parade (1) (Box 32, Folder 11)
  was b20ff69 -- 26 photographs
- Labor Day Parade (2) (Box 32, Folder 12)
  was b20ff69 -- 21 slides; 13 photographs
- Labor Day Parade (3) (Box 32, Folder 13)
  was b20ff69 --
- Labor Day Parade (Box 32, Folder 14)
  was b20ff70 -- 3 photographs
- Labor Day Parade, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  was b20ff71 -- 10 photographs
- Labor Day Parade, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  was b20ff72 -- 6 photographs
- Labor Day Parade - Sept. 2, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  was b20ff73 -- 6 photographs
- Labor Day Parade, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  was b20ff74 -- 1 photograph
- Labor Day Parade, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 19)
- Labor Day Parade - New Jersey, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  was b20ff76 -- 9 photographs
- Labor Day Parade -New York, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  was b20ff77 - 3 photographs
- Labor Day Parade - Sept. 3, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  was b20ff78 -- 5 photographs
- Labor Day Parade - Sept. 2, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  was b20ff79 -- 17 photographs
- Labor Day Parade, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  was b20ff80 -- 5 photographs
- Labor Day Street Fair, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  was b20ff81 -- 2 photographs
- Labor Luncheon - John Hess - 9/1987 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  was b20ff82 - 4 photographs
- Labor Research Assoc. Luncheon - 11/21/1982 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  was b20ff83 -- 6 photographs; news clippings
- Labor Research Assoc. Luncheon -- 12/8/1984 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  was b20ff84 -- 5 photographs; Luncheon program
- Labor/Science Nuclear Dialogue (Box 32, Folder 29)
  was b20ff85 -- 1 photograph
- Betty Lall at Division Boards - 4/1978 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  was b20ff86 -- 1 photographs
- Lampson Dance - May 1953 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  was b20ff87 - 4 photographs
- Lampson Shop Meeting (Box 32, Folder 32)
  was b20ff88 -- 11 photographs
- Lantz - Poca Hontas Tanning (Box 32, Folder 33)
  was b20ff89 -- 1 photograph
- Leather Pension Trustees - 12/5/1974 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  was b20ff90 -- 10 photographs
- Fredy Lee Commencement - 6/8/1984 (Box 32, Folder 35)
  was b20ff91 -- 3 photographs - commencement program
- Legislative Conference - 5/1975 (Box 32, Folder 36)
  was b20ff92 - 4 photographs
- Legislative Day in Fur Industry - 11/12/1985 (Box 32, Folder 37)
  was b20ff93 -- 7 photographs
- Lehigh Valley Annual Meeting -- 11/30/1974 (Box 32, Folder 38)
  was b20ff94 -- 3 photographs
- Lehigh Valley Xmas Party - 12/1972 (Box 32, Folder 39)
  was b20ff95 -- 19 photographs
- Lehigh Valley Xmas party 12/1977 (Box 32, Folder 40)
  was b20ff96 -- 6 photographs
- Lehigh Valley Xmas Party - 12/22/1978 (Box 32, Folder 41)
  was b20ff97 -- 10 photographs
- Lehigh Valley Xmas Party -- 12/1979 (Box 32, Folder 42)
  was b20ff98 -- 9 photographs
- Lehigh Valley Xmas party - 12/13/1980 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  was b20ff99 -- 7 photographs
- Lehigh Valley Xmas Party - 12/5/1981 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  was b20ff100 - 22 photographs
- Lehigh Valley Xmas Party - Dec. 4, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  was b20ff101 -- 21 photographs
- Lehigh Valley meeting - 12/7/1973 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  was b20ff102 -- 2 photographs
- Lehigh Valley Section Party - 12/6/1976 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  was b20ff103 -- 13 photographs
- Ruth Lerner (Box 33, Folder 6)
  was b20ff104 -- 3 photographs
- G. Levor Settlement - Gloversville (Box 33, Folder 7)
  was b20ff105 -- 6 photographs
- Liberal Party Dinner - Javits - 10/31/1985 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  was b20ff106 -- 7 photographs
- Liberal Party Economic Conference - 3/17/1975 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  was b20ff107 -- 2 photographs
- Liberal Party Rally - 10/1978 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  was b20ff108 -- 3 photographs
- LICH Exams - Lee Trujillo (Box 33, Folder 11)
  was b20ff109 -- 3 photographs
- Lincoln Brigade Dinner - 2/1978 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  was b20ff110 -- 1 photograph
- Lincoln Vets Luncheon - 2/25/1979 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  was b20ff111 -- 5 photographs
- Lincoln Vets Luncheon - April 5, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  was b20ff112 -- 5 photographs
- Locals 2 & 3 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  was b20ff113 -- 1 photograph
- Local 2 Outing - March 25-27, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  was b20ff114 -- 1 photograph
- Local 3 Exec. Bd. Meeting -- 3/18/1987; 3/25/1987 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  was b20ff115 -- 2 photographs
- Local 3 - Levest Electric -- 2/1983 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  was b20ff116 -- 3 photographs
- Local 3 Retirees Meeting - 3/24/1987 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  was b20ff117 -- 7 photographs
- Local 27 Housewarming - Feb. 14, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  was b20ff118 -- 6 photographs
- Local 27 Membership Meeting -- 10/12/1967 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  was b20ff119 -- 8 photographs
- Local 27 One Day Institute & Celebration - 10/15/1966 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  was b20ff120 -- 25 photographs
- Local 27 Open House - 10/21/1967 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  was b20ff121 -- 20 photographs
- Local 45 Chicago (Box 33, Folder 24)
  was b20ff122 -- 2 photographs
- Local 48 Pictures (Box 33, Folder 25)
  was b20ff123 -- 12 photographs
- Local 48 Vacation Checks (Box 33, Folder 26)
  was b20ff124 -- 9 photographs
- Local 64 & 61 Membership Meeting -- 5/21/1963 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  was b20ff125 -- 5 photographs
- Locals 64 & 61 Membership Meeting -- 10/9/1964 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  was b20ff126 -- 3 photographs
- Local 64 Membership Meetings (Box 33, Folder 29)
  was b20ff127 -- 10 photographs
- Local 64 Membership Meeting -- 6/15/1954 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  was b20ff128 -- 25 photographs
- Local 64 Membership Meeting -- 5/1957 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  was b20ff129 -- 2 photographs
- Local 64 Membership Meeting - June 1961 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  was b20ff130 - 5 photographs
- Local 64 Membership Mtg. 6/17/1965 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  was b20ff131 -- 8 photographs
- Local 64 News Assorted Pix (Box 33, Folder 34)
  was b20ff132 -- 7 photographs
- Local 64 P & R Reception -- 3/12/1954 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  was b20ff133 -- 7 photographs
- Local 70 Dance -- March 1945 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  was b20ff134 -- 1 photograph
- Local 70 Exec. Bd., 1962 (Box 33, Folder 37)
  was b20ff135 -- 1 photograph
- Local 71 (Minn.) -- Feb. 1942 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  was b20ff136 -- 1 photograph
- Local 85 Executive Board (Box 33, Folder 39)
  was b20ff137 -- 1 photograph
- Local 85 P & R Reception -- 2/24/1955 (Box 33, Folder 40)
  was b20ff138 -- 2 photographs
- Local 88 Membership Meeting (Box 33, Folder 41)
  was b20ff139 -- 1 photograph
- Membership Meeting - Local 88 (Box 33, Folder 42)
  was b20ff140 -- 2 photographs
- Local 88 Membership Meeting (Box 33, Folder 43)
  was b20ff141 -- 2 photographs
- Local 88 Pension Fund - First Checks, 1952 (Box 33, Folder 44)
  was b20ff142 -- 1 photograph
- Local 88 P & R Meeting - 6/1952 (Box 33, Folder 45)
  was b20ff143 -- 5 photographs
- Local 88 Ratification Meeting -- April 1969 (Box 33, Folder 46)
  was b20ff144 -- 9 photographs
- Local 101 Cutters Exec. Bd., 1962 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  was b21f1 - 1 photograph
- Local 105 Operators Exec. Bd., 1962 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  was b21f2 - 1 photograph
- Local 115 Finishers Exec. Bd., 1962 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  was b21f3 -- 1 photograph
- Local 120 Designers Exec. Bd., 1962 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  was b21f4 -- 1 photograph
- Local 125 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  was b21f5 - 6 photographs
- Local 125 Floor Workers Exec. Bd., 1962 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  was b21f6 - 1 photograph
- Local 140 (Hollander) Newark (Box 34, Folder 7)
  was b21f7 -- 2 photograph
- Membership Meeting - Local 150 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  was b21f8 - 2 photographs
- Local 150 Membership Meeting - Oct. 1966 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  was b21f9 -- 10 photographs
- Dr. James Lomax - Retirees Center -- 11/21/1985 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  was b21f10 -- 1 photograph
- Dennis Lovenstein - NY Auction (Minn.) (Box 34, Folder 11)
  was b21f11 -- 3 photographs
- Machines (Box 34, Folder 12)
  was b21f12 -- 4 photographs
- Made in America Meeting - Byior -- 11/25/1985 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  was b21f13 -- 2 photographs
- Manufacturing & Processing Conf. -- 12/1982 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  was b21f14 -- 5 photographs
- Marco Factory Pix - Germany - 4/1970 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  was b21f15 -- 23 photographs
- Jim Martin (Box 34, Folder 16)
  was b21f16 -- 3 photographs
- Marval Strike Meeting - Nov. 1986 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  was b21f17 -- 2 photographs
- Mass Meetings (Box 34, Folder 18)
  was b21f18 -- 17 photographs
- Mass Meetings (Box 34, Folder 19)
  was b21f19 -- 31 photographs
- Roslyn Mathurin Dinner -- 12/16/1983 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  was b21f20 -- 6 photographs
- McAdoo & Allen Contract -- 2/1979 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  was b2121 --
- Dennis McClain Collaring - 4/1979 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  was b21f22 -- 11 photographs -- program
- McCoy Leaflet Material - 4/1975 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  was b21f23 -- 20 photographs
- Willie McGee Demonstration (Box 34, Folder 24)
  was b21f24 -- 3 photographs
- McGovern with Joint Board Staff - March 1969 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  was b21f25 -- EMPTY
- Henry McLeod (Box 34, Folder 26)
  was b21f26
- United Mechanics Membership Meeting -- 11/16/1978 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  was b21f27
- Medicare Demonstration - Washington, D.C. (Box 34, Folder 28)
  was b21f28 - 26 photographs
- Meetings (1) (Box 34, Folder 29)
  was b21f29 -- 26 photographs
- Meetings (2) (Box 34, Folder 30)
- Meetings (3) (Box 34, Folder 31)
- Meetings (4) (Box 34, Folder 32)
- Meetings (5) (Box 34, Folder 33)
  was b21f29 -- 13 photographs
- Meisel - Peskin Blood Pressure Test -- 6/8/1977 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  was b21f30 -- 6 photographs
- Meisel - Peskin Meeting -- Oct. 20, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  was b21f31 -- 6 photographs
- Meisel - Peskin Ratification meeting - Dec. 28, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  was b21f32 -- 2 photographs
- Meisel - Peskin Shop Committee -- 11/1982 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  was b21f33 -- 1 photograph
- Meisel - Peskin Shop Meeting - Martin Luther King Birthday - Jan. 15, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  was b21f34 -- 3 photographs
- Meisel - Peskin Shop Meeting - Nov. 1972 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  was b21f35 -- 1 photograph
- Meisel - Peskin Shop Meeting - Nov. 30, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  was b21f36 -- 3 photographs
- Meisel - Peskin Shop Meeting - 4/7/1974 (Box 34, Folder 41)
  was b21f37 -- 3 photographs
- Meisel - Peskin Shop Meeting - June 14, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 42)
  was b21f38 -- 15 photographs
- Meisel - Peskin Shop Meeting - 6/1976 (Box 34, Folder 43)
  was b21f39 -- 17 photographs
- Meisel - Peskin Shop Meeting - Nov. 19, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 44)
  was b21f40 -- 2 photographs
- Meisel - Peskin Shop Meeting -- 10/1979 (Box 34, Folder 45)
  was b21f41 -- 12 photographs
- Meisel - Peskin Shop Meeting - 3/1980 (Box 34, Folder 46)
  was b21f42 -- 15 photographs
- Meisel - Peskin Shop Meeting - 2/1984 (Box 34, Folder 47)
  was b21f43 -- 4 photographs
- Meisel - Peskin Shop Meeting - 11/1985 (Box 34, Folder 48)
  was b21f44 -- 4 photographs
- Membership Meeting - NY Div. - 2/25/1971 (Box 34, Folder 49)
  was b21f45 -- 10 photographs
- Membership Meetings -- 11/1978 (Box 34, Folder 50)
  was b21f46 - 12 photographs
- Membership Meetings - April, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  was b21f47 -- 2 photographs
- Merger Meeting - 12/3/1985 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  was b21f48 -- 23 photographs
- Metropolitan Labor Press Award - Dec. 1977 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  was b21f49 -- 1 photograph
- Negative of Stamp honoring Chas. Michels, Secy. French Fur & Leather Union (Box 35, Folder 4)
  was b21f50 -- 1 photograph
- Middleville Forum - 6/7/1972 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  was b21f51 -- 3 photographs
- Midwest Conference - Oct. 1941 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  was b21f52 -- 3 photographs
- Mink (Box 35, Folder 7)
  was b21f53 -- 1 photograph
- Misc. (1) (Box 35, Folder 8)
  was b21f54 -- 26 photographs
- Misc. (2) (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Misc. (1) (Box 35, Folder 10)
  was b21f55 -- 26 photographs
- Misc. (2) (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Misc. (3) (Box 35, Folder 12)
  was b21f55 -- 16 photographs
- Misc. (4) (Box 35, Folder 13)
  was b21f55 -- 25 photographs
- Miscellaneous old pictures (Box 35, Folder 14)
  was b21f56 -- 10 photographs
- Mink Blending Contract, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  was b21f57 -- 2 photographs
- Ms. Union Maid (Box 35, Folder 16)
  was b21f58 -- 2 photographs
- Miss Union Maid (Box 35, Folder 17)
  was b21f59 -- 2 photographs
- Molly Maguires (Box 35, Folder 18)
  was b21f60 -- 2 photographs
- Monk Party -- Dec. 9, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  was b21f61 -- 20 photographs
- Murray Montaug - Institute (Box 35, Folder 20)
  was b21f62 --2 photographs
- Montaug Memorial -- 5/16/1985 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  was b21f63 -- 2 photographs
- Montaug Tribute - June 22, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  was b21f64 -- 7 photographs
- Montreal Fur Workers Union (Box 35, Folder 23)
  was b21f65 -- 3 photographs
- Moore Exhibit Opening - 4/27/1970 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  was b21f66 -- 16 photographs
- Moore Stoppage -- NY Auction (Box 35, Folder 25)
  was b21f67 -- 1 photograph
- Morse Baseball Team, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  was b21f68 -- 17 photographs
- Morse Communication Services (Box 35, Folder 27)
  was b21f69 -- 2 photographs
- Morse Electro Products (Box 35, Folder 28)
  was b21f70 -- 4 photographs
- Morse Electro Severance - 1/26/1979 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  was b21f71 -- 4 photographs
- Morse - Mackell -- April 1971 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  was b21f72 -- 3 photographs
- Morse Meeting Contacts - June 24, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  was b21f73
- Morse Meeting - New Workers - 4/15/1975 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  was b21f74 -- 2 photographs
- Morse Negotiating Committee -- 8/1974 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  was b21f75 -- 1 photograph
- Morse negotiations, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  was b21f76 -- 8 photographs
- Morse Outing - June 1973 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  was b21f77 -- 4 photographs
- Morse ratification meeting - Nov. 5, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 36)
  was b21f78 -- 6 photographs
- Morse Safety Ceremony - Nov. 29, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  was b21f79 -- 4 photographs
- Morse Shop Pix - Contacts (Box 35, Folder 38)
  was b21f80 -- 2 photographs
- Mt. Jewett Negotiating Comm., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 39)
  was b21f81 -- 5 photographs
- Mucci Leather Shop - Local 27 (Box 35, Folder 40)
  was b21f82 -- 2 photographs
- Multi-National Conference - 6/19/1982 (Box 35, Folder 41)
  was b21f83 -- 3 photographs
- Multinational Conference -- 10/1983 (Box 35, Folder 42)
  was b21f84 -- 2 photographs
- Murray's Retirement (Box 35, Folder 43)
  was b21f85 -- 11 photographs
- Tom Myerscough (Box 35, Folder 44)
  was b21f86 -- EMPTY
- Nailers Exec. Bd., 1962 (Box 35, Folder 45)
  was b21f87 -- 1 photograph
- NARPPR meeting -- 6/8/1980 (Box 35, Folder 46)
  was b21f88
- Nat'l. Council of Senior Citizens - 6/1980 (Box 35, Folder 47)
  was b21f89 -- 3 photographs
- National Council of Senior citizens Convention - 7/20-22/1983 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  was b21f90 - 4 photographs
- Nat'l. Council of Senior Citizens Convention - June 28-30, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  was b21f91 -- 4 photographs
- Nat'l. Council of Senior citizens - June 1985 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  was b21f92 -- 15 photographs
- Nat'l. Council of Senior Citizens Conventions - 7/1986 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  was b21f93 -- 11 photographs
- Luncheon - Forum Victor Navasky - Oct. 21, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  was b21f94 -- 3 photographs
- Negatives (Exhibit FLM Skills, etc.), 1982 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  was b21f95
- Negro History Celebration, 1954 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  was b21f96 -- 4 photographs
- Negro History Month (Box 36, Folder 8)
  was b21f97 -- 1 photograph
- Neuman & Company FLM at work (Box 36, Folder 9)
  was b21f98 -- 2 photographs
- Neuman & Co. - Shop Meeting - 3/14/1972 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  was b21f99 -- 4 photographs
- R. Neuman Arbitration - 10/21/1982 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  was b21f100 -- 1 photograph
- R. Neuman Christmas Party -- 12/1977 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  was b21f101 -- 1 photograph
- R. Neuman Xmas Party - Dec. 30, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  was b21f102 -- 5 photographs
- R. Neuman Xmas Party -- Dec. 29, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  was b21f103 -- 19 photographs
- R. Neuman Meeting -- 2/13/1975 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  was b21f104 -- 2 photographs
- R. Neuman Negotiations -- April 1983 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  was b21f105 --- EMPTY
- R. Neuman Shop Meeting -- 5/29/1980 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  was b21f106 -- 3 photographs
- R. Neuman Unemployment (Box 36, Folder 18)
  was b21f107 -- 2 photographs
- Newark Christmas Party -- Dec. 1977 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  was b21f109 -- 2 photographs
- Newark Xmas Party -- 12/21/1978 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  was b21f109 -- 1 photograph
- Newark Leather Christmas Party -- 12/18/1980 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  was b21f110 -- 11 photographs
- Newark Xmas Party -- 12/1981 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  was b21f111 -- 10 photographs
- Newark Christmas Party -- 12/1985 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  was b21f112 -- 6 photographs
- Newark Class on Occ. Safety -- 3/1981 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  was b21f113 -- 22 photographs
- Newark Leather Division Board Party -- 12/17/1971 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  was b21f114 -- 6 photographs
- Newark Leather Division Election -- 6/1978 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  was b21f115 -- 7 photographs
- Newark Leather Division Meeting -- 3/19/1975 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  was b21f116 -- 6 photographs
- Newark Leather Division Meeting -- 4/1978 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  was b21f117 -- 9 photographs
- Newark Leather Division Meeting -- 3/28/1979 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  was b21f118 -- 14 photographs
- Newark Leather Division One-Day Institute - 12/6/1975 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  was b21f119 -- 8 photographs
- Newark Leadership Class - 3/1971 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  was b21f120 -- 11 photographs
- Newark Membership meeting - Feb. 23, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  was b21f121 -- 5 photographs
- Newark Membership meeting -- 10/30/1977 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  was b21f122 -- 5 photographs
- Newark Membership Meeting -- 6/25/1980 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  was b21f123 -- 3 photographs
- Newark Leather Membership Meeting -- 4/29/1981 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  was b21f124 -- 4 photographs
- Newark Nominating Meeting -- 4/12/1984 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  was b21f125 -- 1 photograph
- Newark Welfare Meeting -- June 15, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  was b21f126 -- 3 photographs
- N.J. Anti-Trapping Legislation -- 2/1984 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  was b21f127 -- 11 photographs
- N.J. Coalition Against Anti-Trapping Bill -- 8/16/1983 (Box 36, Folder 39)
  was b21f128 -- 6 photographs